Finding Aid for the Centennial History Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Centennial History
multiple
University Archives
RG.0101
1 linear_feet
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1905-1906 (missing)
- Public Service - Reports (9)
- Divinity School - Changing Status - A History
  Photo removed to Photographic Archives - William S. Vaughn Collection
- Administration - Carmichael, Oliver C. Inactive Chancellor 1937-1946
- Happy History - Personal Reminiscences
- Alumni - Quinq - Reminiscences
- Fugitives - Warren, Robert Penn
  files removed to Fugitive Manuscript Collection; photographs removed to Photographic Archives - Fugitive/Agrarian Collection
- Fugitives - Tate, Allen
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1893-1895 (missing)
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1896-1898 (missing)
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1899-1901 (missing)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Faculty Minutes
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1903-1904 (missing)
- Divinity School - Changing Status - A History
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1907-1908 (missing)
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1909-1919 (missing)
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1920-1924 (missing)
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1925-1939 (missing)
- Fugitives - Ransom, John Crowe
- Fugitives - Moore, Merrill
  files removed to Fugitive Manuscript Collection
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material Pre- 1889 (missing)
- Fugitives
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material Undated (missing)
- Agrarians - (Byrd Brief)
- Agrarians
- Administration - Kirkland - Meritt Material 1902 (missing)
- Academic Freedom - "Business Heresy" Complaint (1940) (Box 0019, Folder 1)
- Academic Freedom - 1940's (Box 0019, Folder 2)
- Academic Freedom - 1950's (Box 0019, Folder 3)
- Academic Freedom - 1960's (Box 0019, Folder 4)
- Academic Freedom - 1970's (Box 0019, Folder 5)
- Academic Freedom - Dyer, Gus - 1930's (Box 0019, Folder 6)
- Academic Freedom - 1920's- 1930's (Box 0019, Folder 7)
- Academic Freedom - Extracts from Wilson vs. Vanderbilt University (Box 0019, Folder 8)
- Academic Freedom - O. C. Carmichael, et. al. and The Talmadge Case - 1941 (Box 0019, Folder 9)
- Academic Freedom - Scott, Russell - 1919 (Box 0019, Folder 10)
- Academic Freedom - Executive Committee and Board Minutes - 1949, 1950, 1951 (Box 0019, Folder 11)
- Administration - Trends in University Administration (Box 0019, Folder 12)
- Administration - Board of Trust (Box 0019, Folder 13)
  photo: 1968 BOT group
- Administration - Board of Trust - Officers 1875-1973 (Box 0019, Folder 14)
- Administration - Board of Trust - By-Laws 1872-1959 (Box 0019, Folder 15)
- Administration - Board of Trust - By-Laws Adopted 1960 (Box 0019, Folder 16)
- Administration - Board of Trust - By-Laws 1966, 1970, 1975 (Box 0019, Folder 17)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Alumni Trustees (Box 0019, Folder 18)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Membership Qualifications and lists (Box 0019, Folder 19)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Miscellaneous (Box 0019, Folder 20)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Fitzgerald, Oscar Penn (Box 0019, Folder 21)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Godchaux, Frank (Box 0019, Folder 22)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Hoss, E. E. (Box 0019, Folder 23)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Jenkins, Oscar (Box 0019, Folder 24)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Johnson, Joseph A. (Box 0019, Folder 25)
  first black VU student
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Lake, Devereux (Box 0019, Folder 26)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees McTyeire, Holland N. (Box 0019, Folder 27)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Rand, Frank C. (Box 0019, Folder 28)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Stahlman, James G. (Box 0019, Folder 29)
  photo
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Vanderbilt, Harold S. (Box 0019, Folder 30)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Vaughn, William S. (Box 0019, Folder 31)
- Administration - Board of Trust - Trustees Werthan, Mrs. Mary Jane (Box 0019, Folder 32)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Dowlen Biography (Box 0019, Folder 33)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Biographical Material (Box 0019, Folder 34)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Piston Biographical Sketch (Box 0019, Folder 35)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Family Letters (Box 0019, Folder 36)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Letters #1 (Box 0019, Folder 37)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Letters #2 (Box 0019, Folder 38)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Letters from Europe, 1875 (Box 0019, Folder 39)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Fulton Letters (Box 0019, Folder 40)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Memo Book of N. E. and S. W. Alabama Railroad (Box 0019, Folder 41)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Report to Board May 7, 1889 (Box 0019, Folder 42)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Writings (Box 0019, Folder 43)
- Administration - Kirkland - Conditions of Efficient Faculty Service (Box 0019, Folder 44)
- Administration - Kirkland - Material Miscellaneous (Box 0019, Folder 45)
- Administration - Kirkland - Material to 1930's (Box 0019, Folder 46)
- Administration - Kirkland - Material after 1930 (Box 0019, Folder 47)
- Administration - Kirkland - MS - Book I - Table of Contents, Chapters I and II (Box 0019, Folder 48)
- Administration - Kirkland - MS - Book I - Chapters III, IV, and V (Box 0019, Folder 49)
- Administration - Kirkland - MS - Book I - Chapters VI, VII, VIII, and IX (Box 0019, Folder 50)
- Administration - Kirkland - MS - Book II - Chapters I, II, III, IV, and V (Box 0019, Folder 51)
- Administration - Kirkland - MS - Book III - Chapters I, II, III (Box 0019, Folder 52)
- Administration - Carmichael, Oliver C. Inactive Chancellor 1937-1946 Inauguration, Feb. 3-5, 1938 (Box 0019, Folder 53)
- Administration - Carmichael, Oliver C. Inactive Chancellor 1937-1946 - Clippings (Box 0019, Folder 54)
- Carmichael, Oliver C. Inactive Chancellor 1937-1946 - Speeches (Box 0019, Folder 55)
- Carmichael, Oliver C. Inactive Chancellor 1937-1946 - Releases (Box 0019, Folder 56)
- Carmichael, Oliver C. Inactive Chancellor 1937-1946 - Convocation - February 6, 1946 Honoring Dr. Carmichael (Box 0019, Folder 57)
- Carmichael, Oliver C. Inactive Chancellor 1937-1946 - Biographical and Miscellaneous Materials (Box 0019, Folder 58)
- Administration - Carmichael - re: Intercollegiate Football - 1944 (Box 0019, Folder 59)
- Administration - Carmichael - Piston Biographical Sketch (Box 0019, Folder 60)
- Administration - Carmichael - Papers received from O. C. Carmichael, Jr. (Box 0019, Folder 61)
- Administration - Carmichael - Diary (Box 0019, Folder 62)
- Administration - Carmichael - Biographical (Box 0019, Folder 63)
- Administration - Carmichael - Duncan Interview - MS Notes (Box 0019, Folder 64)
- Administration - Carmichael - Calendar of Speeches (Box 0019, Folder 65)
- Administration - Carmichael - Belgium Relief - Cardinal Mercier's Letter (Box 0019, Folder 66)
- Administration - Carmichael - Selection of (Box 0019, Folder 67)
- Administration - Carmichael - Time, 27 May 1935 (Box 0019, Folder 68)
- Administration - Carmichael - Alumnus articles (1942-1945) (Box 0019, Folder 69)
- Administration - Carmichael - 1938-1946 (Box 0019, Folder 70)
- Administration - Carmichael - Financial Policy - 30 April 1945 (Box 0019, Folder 71)
- Administration - Carmichael - Memorandum on Vanderbilt University 1935-45 (4 Feb. 1946) (Box 0019, Folder 72)
  folder empty
- Administration - Carmichael - 1949-1953 (Box 0019, Folder 73)
- Administration - Carmichael - Post War plans - 8 June 1945 (Box 0019, Folder 74)
- Administration - Carmichael - Correspondence with G. E. B. Officials re: Finances (1939-1944) (Box 0019, Folder 75)
- Administration - Carmichael - Statement of Needs and Program of Development (1938, 1939) (Box 0019, Folder 76)
- Administration - Branscomb - (Selection of) (Box 0020, Folder 1)
- Administration - Branscomb - Memoir - Swint Tapes of Original Memoir (Box 0020, Folder 2)
- Administration - Branscomb - Revised Memoir - Chapters I-VI (Box 0020, Folder 3)
- Administration - Branscomb - Revised Memoir - Chapters VII-XII (Box 0020, Folder 4)
- Administration - Branscomb - Revised Memoir - Chapters XIII-XVIII (Box 0020, Folder 5)
- Administration - Branscomb - Swint-Duncan Interview (typed notes) (Box 0020, Folder 6)
- Administration - Branscomb - Ms and Typescripts from Harvie Branscomb (Box 0020, Folder 7)
- Administration - Branscomb - Memoir - Transcription of Swint Tapes of Original Memoir (Box 0020, Folder 8)
- Administration - Branscomb and the Board of Trust (Box 0020, Folder 9)
- Administration - Branscomb - Biographical Sketch (Piston) (Box 0020, Folder 10)
- Administration - Branscomb - Miscellaneous 1946-1952 (Box 0020, Folder 11)
- Administration - Branscomb - Miscellaneous 1957-1973 (Box 0020, Folder 12)
- Administration - Branscomb - Miscellaneous - Tapes of Interviews (Box 0020, Folder 13)
- Administration - Branscomb - Report to Board of Trust, May 1962 (Box 0020, Folder 14)
- Administration - Branscomb - The Race Problem... 1946-1963 (Box 0020, Folder 15)
- Administration - Branscomb - Vanderbilt's National Role (Box 0020, Folder 16)
- Administration - Branscomb - Federal Funds (Box 0020, Folder 17)
- Administration - Branscomb - Peabody Vanderbilt Relations (Box 0020, Folder 18)
- Administration - Evolution - Huxley, Thomas (1876) (Box 0020, Folder 19)
- Administration - Evolution - American Association for the Advancement of Science (1877) (Box 0020, Folder 20)
- Administration - Evolution - After 1900 (Box 0020, Folder 21)
- Administration - Evolution - Winchell, Alexander (Box 0020, Folder 22)
- Administration - Book - Vanderbilt Alumnus (Box 0020, Folder 23)
- Administration - Heard - Biographical and Bibliographical (Box 0020, Folder 24)
- Administration - Heard - (Selection of) (Box 0020, Folder 25)
- Administration - Heard - Ten Years: 1963-1973 Transcript (Box 0020, Folder 26)
- Administration - Heard - To 1963 (Box 0020, Folder 27)
- Administration - Heard - 1963-1967 (Box 0020, Folder 28)
- Administration - Heard - 1967-1972 (Box 0020, Folder 29)
- Administration - Heard - 1972-1975 (Box 0020, Folder 30)
- Administration - Heard - Presidential Advisor (1970) (Box 0020, Folder 31)
- Administration - Heard - "The Heard Decade" 1963-1973 (Box 0020, Folder 32)
- Administration - Heard - Complaints (1968-1969) (Box 0020, Folder 33)
- Administration - Heard - Interview, 23 July 1970 Tapes (Box 0020, Folder 34)
- Administration - Heard - Transcript of Taped Interview, 23 July 1970 -1- (Box 0020, Folder 35)
- Administration - Heard - Transcript of Taped Interview, 23 July 1970 -2- (Box 0020, Folder 36)
- Administration - Heard - (Piston Brief) (Box 0020, Folder 37)
- Administration - Deans of Women (Box 0020, Folder 38)
- Administration - Faculty (Box 0020, Folder 39)
- Administration - Faculty - Awards (Box 0020, Folder 40)
- Administration - Faculty - Benefits (Box 0020, Folder 41)
- Administration - Faculty - Biographical Data - Promotions and Appointments (1969) (Box 0020, Folder 42)
- Administration - Faculty - Committees (Wednesday, 29 September 1971) (Box 0020, Folder 43)
- Administration - Faculty - Publications Orientalia (Box 0020, Folder 44)
- Administration - Faculty - Publications and Research (Box 0020, Folder 45)
- Administration - Faculty - Register 1875-1925 (Box 0020, Folder 46)
- Administration - Faculty - Tenure (Box 0020, Folder 47)
- Administration - Faculty - Responsibility and Appointment and Tenure Policies, 1971 (Box 0020, Folder 48)
- Administration - Faculty - Research Council (Bradley Material) (Box 0020, Folder 49)
- Administration - Faculty - University Senate Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 0020, Folder 50)
- Administration - Faculty - University Senate Minutes (Scattered issues 1967-1972) (Box 0020, Folder 51)
- Administration - Faculty - University Senate (Box 0020, Folder 52)
- Administration - Faculty - Reports of the Committee Responsibility (1968, 1969, 1971) (Box 0020, Folder 53)
- Administration - Faculty - Salaries 1879 (Box 0020, Folder 54)
- Administration - Faculty - Salaries - Correspondence between Kirkland and GEB Officials, 1920-1926 (Box 0020, Folder 55)
- Administration - Faculty - Salaries 1920; 1955-1956 (Box 0020, Folder 56)
- Administration - Finances - 1973 Income, Endowment, and Comparison (Box 0020, Folder 57)
- Administration - Finances - Alumni Donations (Box 0020, Folder 58)
- Administration - Finances - Branscomb and Federal Money (Box 0020, Folder 59)
- Administration - Finances - Correspondence (Box 0020, Folder 60)
- Administration - Finances - Development Foundation (Box 0020, Folder 61)
  folder is empty
- Administration - Finances - Endowment, Income and Expenditure 1875-1965 (Box 0020, Folder 62)
- Administration - Finances - 1922 Report of the College (Box 0020, Folder 63)
- Administration - Finances - University Budgets (Box 0020, Folder 64)
- Administration - Finances - Retirement and other Benefits (Box 0020, Folder 65)
- Administration - Finances - Vanderbilt Gifts (Box 0020, Folder 66)
- Administration - Finances - 1923-1939 (Box 0020, Folder 67)
- Administration - Finances - 1966-1970 (Box 0020, Folder 68)
- Administration - Finances - 1971- (Box 0020, Folder 69)
- Administration - Finances - 1905-1973 Comparison…Tuition and Endowment Income (Box 0020, Folder 70)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - G. E. B. (General Education Board ) (Box 0020, Folder 71)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - Rockefeller, Laura Spelman (Box 0020, Folder 72)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - To 1950 (Box 0020, Folder 73)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - Nov. 1928 to June 1929 Contributions (Box 0020, Folder 74)
  G. E. B., Carnegie Corp., Laura Spelman Rockefeller, and Vanderbilt Family
- Administration - (Major) Finance - G. E. B./Rockefeller Correspondence (Box 0020, Folder 75)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - Ford (Box 0020, Folder 76)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - 1950- (Box 0020, Folder 77)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - Mellon (Box 0020, Folder 78)
- Administration - (Major) Finance - Carnegie (Box 0020, Folder 79)
- Administration - Chancellor Garland - Report to Board July 7, 1887 (Box 0020, Folder 80)
- Administration - Integration (Box 0020, Folder 81)
- Administration - Integration (Sarratt's File) (Box 0020, Folder 82)
- Administration - Heard - Speeches - NOT Cross-Indexed 1963-1966 (noted by HLS, 1977) (Box 0020, Folder 83)
- Administration - Vice-Chancellor - Kaludis, George (Box 0020, Folder 84)
- Administration - Vice-Chancellor - Poindexter, John (Box 0021, Folder 1)
- Administration - Vice-Chancellor - for Medical Affairs (Box 0021, Folder 2)
- Administration - Vice-Chancellor - Sarratt, C. Madison (Box 0021, Folder 3)
- Administration - Vice-Chancellor - Sarratt, C. Madison (Box 0021, Folder 4)
- Administration - Vice-Chancellor - Sarratt, C. Madison Taped Interview 15 August 1969 (Box 0021, Folder 5)
- Administration - Miscellaneous (Box 0021, Folder 6)
- Administration - Miscellaneous - Cordell Hull Foundation (Box 0021, Folder 7)
- Administration - Miscellaneous - Patent Policy (Box 0021, Folder 8)
- Administration - Miscellaneous - University Governance (Box 0021, Folder 9)
- Administration - Miscellaneous - Women's Status (Box 0021, Folder 10)
- Administration - Organization (Box 0021, Folder 11)
- Administration - Organization - Changes 1972 (Box 0021, Folder 12)
- Administration - Organization - Chart (Box 0021, Folder 13)
- Administration - Organization - 2 February 1954 (Box 0021, Folder 14)
- Administration - Organization - Manuel…of the Schools and Colleges [sic] 1955 (Box 0021, Folder 15)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Architecture and Architects (Box 0021, Folder 16)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Pictures (Box 0021, Folder 17)
- Survey of Printing at VU 1977-78 (Box 0021, Folder 18)
  office of Opportunity Dev. Officer requested the survey
- Administration - Physical Plant - Acreage March 1, 1971 (Box 0021, Folder 19)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Bryan, E. E. notes (Box 0021, Folder 20)
- Administration - Physical Plant - McGugin Center (Box 0021, Folder 21)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Roberts, Erb (Box 0021, Folder 22)
- Administration - Physical Plant - 1875-1969, Statistics (Architects, Contractors, Costs, etc.) (Box 0021, Folder 23)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Major Campus Construction 1874-1973, Table and Footnotes (Box 0021, Folder 24)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Computer Center (Box 0021, Folder 25)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Map from Planning Office (Box 0021, Folder 26)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Magruder Center (Box 0021, Folder 27)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Day and Klauder Plan - VU Campus (Box 0021, Folder 28)
  Proposed Plan Shows Topographical Contours and Grades
- Administration - Physical Plant - Alumni Hall (Box 0021, Folder 29)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Barnard Observatory (Box 0021, Folder 30)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Buttrick Hall (Box 0021, Folder 31)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Calhoun Hall (Box 0021, Folder 32)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Highlands of N. C. - "Dearmont" (Box 0021, Folder 33)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Campus Expansion, proposed 6/16/59 (Clarke and Rapuano) (Box 0021, Folder 34)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Campus area shows topographical buildings as of c. 1960 (Box 0021, Folder 35)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Campus Plan 1985 (Box 0021, Folder 36)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Chancellor, Res. (near hospital) Res 8 (Box 0021, Folder 37)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Engineering Building (old) (Box 0021, Folder 38)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Fine Arts Building (old gym) (Box 0021, Folder 39)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Fraternity/ Sorority area (Box 0021, Folder 40)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Garland Avenue Buildings (Box 0021, Folder 41)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Garland Hall (Box 0021, Folder 42)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Hospital and Medical Center (Box 0021, Folder 43)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Joint University Library (Box 0021, Folder 44)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Kirkland Hall (Box 0021, Folder 45)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Kissam Hall (Box 0021, Folder 46)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Mary Henderson Hall (Box 0021, Folder 47)
- Administration - Physical Plant - McTyeire Hall (Box 0021, Folder 48)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Neely Auditorium (Box 0021, Folder 49)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Old Aerial Photo VU area (Box 0021, Folder 50)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Old Central Building (Box 0021, Folder 51)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Old Gym addition (Box 0021, Folder 52)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Plant Operations Office Building (Box 0021, Folder 53)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Power House (Box 0021, Folder 54)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Property Ownership Map, VU through about 1965 (Box 0021, Folder 55)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # (Foremans) (Box 0021, Folder 56)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # 4 (Hart) (Box 0021, Folder 57)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # (Jackson) (Box 0021, Folder 58)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # (McGill) (Box 0021, Folder 59)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # (Mims) (Box 0021, Folder 60)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # 6 (Owsley) (Box 0021, Folder 61)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # 7 (Paschel) (Box 0021, Folder 62)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Science Hall (Box 0021, Folder 63)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Res. # 5 (Tillett) (Box 0021, Folder 64)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Topographic map - VU Campus (Box 0021, Folder 65)
- Administration - Physical Plant - University Center 1961 (Box 0021, Folder 66)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Vanderbilt University Plot Plan c. 1962-1964 showing parking (Box 0021, Folder 67)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Wesley Hall (new) (Box 0021, Folder 68)
- Administration - Physical Plant - West Side Hall (Box 0021, Folder 69)
- Administration - Physical Plant - West Side Row (Box 0021, Folder 70)
- Administration - Physical Plant - 2315 West End (Box 0021, Folder 71)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Maps and Plans (Box 0021, Folder 72)
- Administration - Physical Plant - (Box 0021, Folder 73)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Medical (Box 0021, Folder 74)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Articles, Clippings, News Releases and Pamphlets (Box 0021, Folder 75)
- Administration - Provost, Deputy - Clanton, Glen (Box 0021, Folder 76)
- Administration - Provost, Asst. - Wilcoxon, Reba (Box 0021, Folder 77)
- Administration - Provost, Executive Vice-Chancellor - Surface, James (Box 0021, Folder 78)
- Administration - Provost, Hobbs, Nicholas (Box 0021, Folder 79)
- Administration - Provost, "A Report on the Academic Programs" Hobbs, Nicholas (Box 0021, Folder 80)
- Administration - Public Service (Box 0021, Folder 81)
- Administration - Staff (Women) (Box 0021, Folder 82)
- Administration - Staff - Secretary of the University - McGaw, Robert A. (Box 0021, Folder 83)
- Administration - Staff - Treasurer - Halliburton, Gus G. (Box 0021, Folder 84)
- Administration - Staff - Chief of Campus Security - Blankenship, Robert (Box 0021, Folder 85)
- Administration - Staff - Labor Relations and Recruiting Problems (Box 0021, Folder 86)
- Administration - University Curriculum - Development (Box 0021, Folder 87)
- Administration - University Curriculum - Interdisciplinary Program - English School Integrated Degree (Box 0021, Folder 88)
- Administration - University Curriculum - Interdisciplinary Program (Box 0021, Folder 89)
- Alumni (Box 0021, Folder 90)
- Alumni - Reunion '73 (tapes, etc.) (Box 0021, Folder 91)
- Alumni Associations (Box 0021, Folder 92)
- Alumni - Quinq - Adams, Alfred G. (Box 0021, Folder 93)
- Alumni - Quinq - Long, Rev. Charles (Box 0021, Folder 94)
- Alumni - Quinq - Meetings 6/3/72 and 5/31/75 (Box 0021, Folder 95)
- Associations and Societies (Box 0021, Folder 96)
- Associations and Societies - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 0021, Folder 97)
- Centennial History - Common Law Copyright (Box 0021, Folder 98)
- Centennial History - Filing Procedures and Guide (including bibliographic files) (Box 0021, Folder 99)
- Centennial History - Prospectus (Box 0021, Folder 100)
- Centennial History - Bibliographical Information for VU Bulletin (Box 0021, Folder 101)
- Centennial History - Prospectus and Abstract of Outline (Box 0021, Folder 102)
- Centennial History - Outline 1975 (Box 0021, Folder 103)
- Centennial History - Calendar (Box 0021, Folder 104)
- Centennial History - Manual of Style - Abbreviated - May 1976 (Box 0021, Folder 105)
- Centennial History - Manual of Style May 1976 (Box 0021, Folder 106)
- Centennial History - Manual of Style (Box 0021, Folder 107)
- Centennial History - Miscellaneous Equipment Instruction (Box 0021, Folder 108)
- Centennial History - U. S. Government Library Photocopying Guidelines (Box 0021, Folder 109)
- Centennial History - Miscellaneous Items (Box 0021, Folder 110)
- Baldwin, Robert (Box 0021, Folder 111)
- Batson, Randolph (Vice-Chancellor Medical Affairs) (Box 0021, Folder 112)
- Batts, William O. (University Registrar) Correspondence (Box 0021, Folder 113)
- Beach, Leonard B. (Dean of the Graduate School) (Box 0021, Folder 114)
- Belcher, Jan (News Bureau) (Box 0021, Folder 115)
- Blankenship, Robert (Campus Security) (Box 0021, Folder 116)
- Boutwell, Dean Sidney (Box 0021, Folder 117)